NGUYỄN VIỆT HÙNG

.NET DEVELOPER



0395746139



hnv2311@gmail.com P Ho Chi Minh City





23/11/2001



portfolio.hocduthu.com

PROFILE INFO

.NET developer with 1 year of experience developing web and web API applications using .NET Core, SQL Server, MySQL. Understanding OOP principles, software development methodologies, git version control, and agile practices. Self-motivated, proactive, and capable of working independently as well as in a team environment, and also ability to analyze and design databases

EXPERIENCE

Jul 2024 - Present

Vũ Thảo Software Solution | R&D Department

.NET Developer

- Data migration tool: Implement a tool to migrate data from the old system to the new system for the client Becamex Binh Phước using SharePoint, Winform, SQL Server stored procedures
- AppGroup Feature for Digital Process Management project (DPM):
 - + Create an admin configuration screen and an end-user display screen for managing application groups
 - + Develop APIs to retrieve and update data for the AppGroup feature
 - + Write SQL Server stored procedures to manage database interactions
- Menu Feature Upgrade (DPM project) :
 - + Update the left menu and user profile menu with the new interface
 - + Add top menu for improved navigation
 - + Migrate the data source from SharePoint to SQL for better performance and scalability

Dec 2023 - May 2024

P&B Food Viet Nam I Thu Dau Mot City, Binh Duong Province

Freelancer Fulltime

- Auth Module: Implement ASP.NET Identity and JWT with authentication and authorization features, including refresh token functionality
- Payment Integration Module: Develop functions for PayOs and Momo payment gateway transactions via API
- Background Job Module: Use Hangfire for scheduled tasks (e.g., daily order summaries, email sending)
- Deployment: Utilize GitHub Actions to trigger and process code builds into Docker images

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

FPT Software I District 9, Ho Chi Minh City

.Net Intern

· Analyze existing application code, write unit tests, and debug the application

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 | FPT University

Software Engineering

SKILLS

Programming languages:

• C#, Java, JavaScript

Framework:

- .Net (Core, Framework)
- SharePoint Server

Database:

• SQL Server, Stored Procedure

Cloud:

Basic Azure, VPS

Others:

- · GitHub, Redis
- HTML, CSS, Jquery
- · Linux OS, Docker
- English

CERTIFICATE

Linux Fundamentals

Computer Communications

(2)

Google Project Management

0 0

Software Development Lifecycle